Welcome to the first section of the course.
And in this section you're gonna learn
the very basics of the Javascript language.
Things like variables, data types, functions,
objects, erase, and many other things
that are part of the Javascript language.
And the best part is that you're actually
not just gonna learn Javascript itself
but at the same time the fundamentals of programming
in general.
Now later in the course we're actually gonna come back
to many of these fundamentals.
But for now, I just want you to get a quick overview
of how the language works and get your hands dirty
with some coding.
So this part of the course is really not about
making things look pretty in a browser
or anything like that.
Right now we just wanna focus on
the Javascript language itself and then the rest
will come later.
All right.
So let's go start this journey right now.